{
    "subject": "resource/Spoetzl_Brewery",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundingYear",
    "object": "1909",
    "human_readable": "Spoetzl Brewery was founded in 1909.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9383889436721802,
            "question": "When was Spoetzl Brewery founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9330917000770569,
            "question": "Who founded Spoetzl Brewery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6985180974006653,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the history of Spoetzl Brewery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6843948364257812,
            "question": "What year did Spoetzl Brewery begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6361982822418213,
            "question": "Is there a famous beer associated with Spoetzl Brewery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.518143892288208,
            "question": "How long has Spoetzl Brewery been in existence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45619308948516846,
            "question": "Is Spoetzl Brewery a new or old company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44879865646362305,
            "question": "Where is Spoetzl Brewery located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3420373499393463,
            "question": "What products does Spoetzl Brewery produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3030523657798767,
            "question": "What type of business is Spoetzl Brewery?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Spoetzl Brewery was founded in 1909.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4445_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What products does Spoetzl Brewery produce?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4445_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Spoetzl Brewery located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4445_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Spoetzl Brewery a new or old company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4445_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4445_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that \"Spoetzl Brewery was founded in 1909\". All five documents mention that Spoetzl Brewery was founded in 1909, with one document even specifying that it was originally known as the Shiner Brewing Association and founded by Czech and German immigrants."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that the Spoetzl Brewery was founded in 1909, which supports the statement \"Spoetzl Brewery was founded in 1909.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}